buzzvideo.com 2018-06-21

# TopBuzz - Top Video, GIFs, TV, News

#### If you are a user located in the European Union, click here

* * *

Welcome to Topbuzz/BuzzVideo (the “Platform”). The Platform is provided or controlled by Bytedance Inc. (“we” or “us”). We committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

We are registered in the State of Delaware, United States of America under company number 5943290 and have our registered office at 1013 Centre Road, Suite 403-B and our primary business location at Building No. 1, Zhong Hang Plaza, No. 43, North 3rd Ring Road West, Haidian District, Beijing, People’s Republic of China.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By accessing or using our website, services, applications, products and content (that include but are not limited to the Platform) (collectively, the “Services”), you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this policy have the meaning given to them in the Terms of Service.

### 1\. The Types of Personal Data We Use

We may collect and use the following information about you:

  * Information you give us. You may give us information about you by accessing or using our Services or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register for and/or use the Platform, such as your customer profile, information about your device, your browsing records, the comments you make on our Platform, as well as account details. The information you give us may include your name, address, email address, social media login details, telephone number. It also includes information that you give to us, such as user-generated content and video content that you may choose to broadcast on our Platform.
  * Information you choose to share from your social networks. If you choose to link the Platform to your social network or public forum account (such as Facebook or WeChat), you may provide us or allow your social network to provide us with information from your social network or public forum accounts. This data may include your use of the Platform on such public forums and/or social networks. For further information as to how and for what purpose the social network provider processes your data, please see their privacy policies.
  * Information we collect about you. We automatically collect certain data from you, including IP address or other unique device identifiers, Cookies (as defined below), mobile carrier, time zone and locale setting, mobile or device model, operating system and platform and information regarding your use of the Platform. We will collect behavioural information, for example profiles and your presumed interests, alongside marketing information such as opt-ins and communication preferences. We may also collect information about linking your contact or subscriber information with your activity across our Platform or by linking your activity on our Platform across all your devices using your email or social media log-in details.
  * Location data. When you use the Platform on a mobile device, we may process information about your location, including location information based on your SIM card, IP address or mobile device location settings, and if activated on your mobile device, by use of a Global Positioning System (GPS). We may use such information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising and other personalised content. If you do not wish to share your GPS location with us, you can switch off GPS functionality on your mobile device.
  * Information from third parties. We may receive information if you use any of the other websites we operate or other Services we provide. We may also receive information from third party SDKs, and from other sources, including business directories and other commercially or publicly available sources.

### 2\. Cookies

We use cookies and other similar technologies (e.g. web beacons, Flash cookies, etc.) (“Cookies”) to enhance your experience using the Platform. Cookies are small files which, when placed on your device, enable us to provide certain features and functionality.

We use the following Cookies:

  * Strictly necessary Cookies. These are Cookies that are required for the operation of the Platform. They include, for example, Cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of the Platform.
  * Functionality Cookies. These are used to recognise you when you return to the Platform. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
  * Targeting Cookies. These Cookies record your visit to the Platform, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make the Platform and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

If for any reason you wish to not take advantage of Cookies, you may disable Cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you do so, this will affect your enjoyment of the Platform and we will no longer be able to offer to you personalised content. Unless you opt out of Cookies, we will assume you consent to the use of Cookies.

“Do-not-track” signals are preferences that users can set on their web browser to limit how their activity is tracked across third-party websites or online services. The Platform does not respond to “do-not-track” signals in your web browser.

### 3\. How We Use Your Personal Data

We will use the information in the following ways:

  * In accordance with our contract with you, we may use your information to:
    * personalise the content you receive and provide you with tailored content that may be of interest to you;
    * notify you about changes to our Services;
    * provide you with user support;
    * enforce our terms, conditions and policies; or
    * communicate with you.
  * As it is in our legitimate interests to be responsive to you and to ensure the proper functioning of our products and organisation, we may use your information to:
    * improve the Platform and to ensure content from the Platform is presented in the most effective manner for you and your device;
    * administer the Platform and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
    * allow you to participate in interactive features of the Platform, when you choose to do so;
    * personalise the content you receive;
    * keep the Platform safe and secure;
    * develop our Platform and conduct product development;
    * measure and understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you and others;
    * make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of the Platform about goods or services that may interest you or them; or
    * provide you – or permit selected third parties to provide you – with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. Where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

It is in our legitimate interests to promote the Platform, and by agreeing to comply with this policy you agree that we may use information that you give to us, such as user-generated content and video content that you may choose to broadcast on our Platform, as part of our advertising and marketing campaigns to promote the Platform.

We may share your personal data with selected third parties in or outside your country, including:

  * our business partners so that we can make you special offers via the Platform;
  * with respect to on-screen advertisements, advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve advertisements to you and others. We will not share your contact details with our business parties so they will not contact you directly, but we will share other information so that they can make you offers tailored to your requirements;
  * our suppliers and subcontractors who help us run the Platform; or
  * analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of the Platform.

We may share your information with any member or affiliate of our group, which includes our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, and companies that we control, are controlled or under common control, and our service providers and strategic business partners, and their respective subsidiaries, in each case in or outside your country, for the purposes set out above (“How We Use Your Personal Data”). For Japanese personal data only, Bytedance Inc. continues to be primarily responsible for protection of your information.

We may share your information with law enforcement agencies, public or tax authorities or other organisations if legally required to do so, or if we have a good faith belief that such use is reasonably necessary to:

  * comply with a legal obligation, process or request (including tax and related reporting requirements);
  * enforce our Terms of Service and other agreements, policies, and standards, including investigation of any potential violation thereof;
  * detect, prevent or otherwise address security, fraud or technical issues; or
  * protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users, a third party or the public as required or permitted by law (including exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction).

We may also disclose your information to third parties:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; or
  * if we sell, buy, merge, are acquired by, or partner with other companies or businesses, or sell some or all of our assets. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets.

### 5\. Where We Store Your Personal Data

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside of your country and the European Economic Area (“EEA”), specifically, to third party servers in the United States and Singapore. It may also be processed by staff operating outside your country or the EEA who work for us, for one of our suppliers or one of our business partners. By submitting your information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.

### 6\. The Security of Your Personal Data

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted through the Platform; any transmission is at your own risk.

We may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any information to these websites.

### 7\. Data Retention

  * We will retain your information for so long as we are required to retain such information under applicable laws.

After you have terminated your use of our services, we may store your information in an aggregated and anonymised format. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may also retain any personal information as reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, allow us to resolve and litigate disputes, and to enforce our agreements.

### 8\. Information Relating to Children

The Platform is not directed at children under the age of 16 (or to persons under the age of: (i) 13 in the United States; (ii) 18 in Brazil; and (iii) 20 in Japan). Users under the relevant age are not allowed to use the Platform or register an account on the Platform without the consent of their parent of guardian. If we become aware that personal data has been collected from a person under such age in the relevant jurisdiction and parental or guardian consent has not been provided, we will delete this information and terminate the person’s account. If you believe that we may have personal data about or collected from a child under the specified age in the relevant jurisdiction without the consent of their parent or guardian, please contact us at supporten@topbuzz.com.

### 9\. Complaints

In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how we process your personal data, please contact us in the first instance at supporten@topbuzz.com and we will endeavour to deal with your request as soon as possible. This is without prejudice to your right to launch a claim with your data protection authority or follow the dispute resolution process provided in the Terms of Service.

### 10\. Changes

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to generally notify all users of any material changes to this policy, such as through a notice on our Platform, however, you should look at this policy regularly to check for such changes. We will also update the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy, which reflects the effective date of such policy. Your continued access to or use of the Services after the date of the updated policy constitutes your acceptance of the updated policy. If you do not agree to the updated policy, you must stop accessing or using the Services.

### 11\. Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy are welcomed and should be addressed to supporten@topbuzz.com.

In the event of a conflict between the provisions of the Supplemental Terms – Jurisdiction-Specific that are relevant to your jurisdiction from which you access or use the Services, and the rest of policy, the relevant jurisdictions’ Supplemental Terms – Jurisdiction-Specific will supersede and control.

Brazil. If you are using our services in Brazil, the following additional terms apply:

  * Parental and Guardian Consent. If you are over the age of 16 but under the age of 18, you declare that you had the consent of your parent or legal guardian to use the Platforms or to register an account on the Platforms.
  * Your Rights
    * Marketing. You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for email or text marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at supporten@topbuzz.com.
    * Data Rights. You have the right to access information we hold about you, to rectify any personal data held about you that is inaccurate, to receive a copy of the data we hold about you in a structured, commonly-used and machine readable format, and to request the deletion of personal data held about you after termination of the relation between you and us, except for the cases in which we were legally obliged to retain your information. You can exercise your rights by contacting us at supporten@topbuzz.com.

Japan. If you are using our services in Japan, the following additional terms apply:

  * Parental and Guardian Consent. If you are over the age of 16 but under the age of 20, you declare that you had the consent of your parent or legal guardian to use the Platforms or to register an account on the Platforms.
  * How We Share Your Personal Data. Notwithstanding the information set out above (“How We Share Your Personal Data”), in Japan we share your personal data only with selected third parties expressly listed in that section.
  * Your Rights
    * Marketing. You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for email or text marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at supporten@topbuzz.com.
    * Data Rights. You have the right to access personal data we hold about you, to rectify any personal data held about you that is inaccurate, to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you in a paper format or a structured, commonly-used and machine readable format, and to request the deletion of personal data held about you. You can exercise your rights by contacting us at supporten@topbuzz.com.

United States. If you are using our services in the United States, the following additional terms apply:

  * Your Rights
    * Data Rights. You have the right to access personal data we hold about you, to rectify any personal data held about you that is inaccurate, to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you in a structured, commonly-used and machine readable format, and to request the deletion of personal data held about you. You can exercise your rights by contacting us at supporten@topbuzz.com.
    * Marketing. You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for email or text marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at supporten@topbuzz.com.
    * Your California privacy rights. California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Services that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail or write us at the “Contact Us” information below.
    * Contact Us: Users in the United States can contact us with questions about our policy by sending an email to supporten@topbuzz.com.
